Chugging and chuffing along the ocean listening to cries of seagulls
Rolling and roiling waves rocking the boat I’m sailing to the isle
Island of the occult
My mind is racing and my heart is thumping...
Surging ecstasy! Savoring the taste of curiosity!
Time after time after time   I studied the contents of the cursed grimoires
Mulled over page after page   The whole thing nothing but gobbledegook
...But! Goodbye, worrying!
And adios to my days of inside living
I am here at last, standing on the shore of an isle of mystery!
Only one who cracks the code can enter this spacious room and
Gosh, how bright it shines...
There and everywhere is gold and more gold!
Yahoo! Pa Pa Ya! Ah...
Knowing all along that this is the fruit of a forbidden paradise
(zero seven fifteen eleven twenty-nine)
Clash clatter zip swish thunk   Dreadful noises are coming from somewhere
Must be mistaken, I think   There shouldn’t be anybody here but me
What is this island’s deal...?
Pretending not to notice worry rising,
I followed the noise and let myself be drawn in deeper, deeper still...
Golden butterfly breed
Septuple stakes that clatter round at high speed
Blades and barriers lead
To red text and even blue to read
Yep, screw this, I am out! Goodbye forever, you occultic island
You can bet your life I will never dare to set foot here again...
But fear strikes, I’m trapped in here
And the words I shout out are,
“Where on Earth am I?!”
“A perverted region packed with witches?!”
Oh No! My God... Ha...!!
Then the legend’s lost, hidden alongside a very fishy fruit
(zero seven fifteen eleven twenty-nine)